

SRI PADMANABAN G

+91 9659289012 paddusribu333@gmail.com

No.8 Naatamai Garden, Ramasamy Muthaliyaar Street, Kochadai, Madurai - 625016

Summary

Forward-thinking Graphic Designer with 1+ years of experience. I have confidence in my ability to facilitate positive change and collective effort. Waiting to grab opportunity and set myself a goal where I can be innovative and attain a challenging position by exercising my interpersonal and professional skills to the fullest for the growth of the organization and mine as well.

Skills

- Adobe Photoshop
- CorelDraw
- 2D Animation
- Illustrator

- Adobe Premier Pro
- InDesign
- After effects
- Graphic Design

Work Experience

Organization: Client8mediaake Pvt. Ltd., MADURAI

Designation: JUNIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Duration : September 2022 till date

- Establish and manage a freelance graphic design business that aims to assist companies in brand development
- Develop creative advertising content for various media, including catalogs, menus, business cards, flyers, posters, t-shirts and product packaging while ensuring maximum brand awareness of target audience/market
- Leverage rebranding expertise in enhancing client's corporate image to ensure profitability and business growth
- Conceptualize logo design, videos, websites and social media channels promote product brands

Organization: SBL Knowledge Service Pvt. Ltd., MADURAI

Designation: JUNIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Duration: October 2021 to July 2022

- Collaborated with Photographer Assistant to collect, edit and process all digital image (2D)
- Created advertisement, invitations and portrait editing using Adobe photoshop
- Designed and Created logos for branding and identity using Illustrator and CorelDraw
- Experienced in Microsoft Office including Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Premier Pro and Photoshop
- Designed photos and sketches for t-shirts via Adobe Premier Pro

Organization: SBL Knowledge Service Pvt. Ltd., MADURAI

Designation : GRAPHIC DESIGNER INTERN

Duration: July 2021 to October 2021

• Collaborated with Photographer Assistant to collect, edit (hair masking, background correction, clipping, isolation, etc.,) and process all digital image

Organization: Dictionary Photography, MADURAI

Designation: **GRAPHIC DESIGNER Duration**: March 2021 to June 2021

- Designed several pieces of print collateral including brochures, special event invitations viasmudge art.
- Edited photos and videos for album designing using Vector art.

Education

- MK University (B.Sc. Computer Science), Madurai 2018 to 2021
- St. Mary's Hr. sec. school (HSC), Madurai 2010
- St. Mary's Hr. sec. school (SSLC), Madurai 2008

Work Samples

• https://www.behance.net/a8ba6ad7

LinkedIn

• https://www.linkedin.com/in/g-sri-padmanaban-749704155

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that all the information provided above is true and the best of my knowledge and belief.

Place: Madurai

Date: (Sri Padmanaban G)